{
    "subject": "resource/The_Time,_the_Place_and_the_Girl_(1929_film)",
    "predicate": "property/studio",
    "object": "resource/Vitaphone",
    "human_readable": "The film 'The Time, the Place and the Girl' was produced by Vitaphone.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9883133172988892,
            "question": "Is 'The Time, the Place and the Girl' a film production by Vitaphone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9413789510726929,
            "question": "Who produced the film 'The Time, the Place and the Girl'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9383823275566101,
            "question": "What film was produced by Vitaphone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9324306845664978,
            "question": "Name a film produced by Vitaphone."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.909381628036499,
            "question": "What is the name of the film produced by Vitaphone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9047399759292603,
            "question": "Was 'The Time, the Place and the Girl' a movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8344230055809021,
            "question": "Is Vitaphone known for producing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8057301640510559,
            "question": "Which company was responsible for producing 'The Time, the Place and the Girl'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7457959055900574,
            "question": "Who might have directed 'The Time, the Place and the Girl'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2649071216583252,
            "question": "What type of media company is Vitaphone?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film 'The Time, the Place and the Girl' was produced by Vitaphone.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2938_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who might have directed 'The Time, the Place and the Girl'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2938_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which company was responsible for producing 'The Time, the Place and the Girl'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2938_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Vitaphone known for producing films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2938_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2938_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2938_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2938_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2938_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2938_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2938_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2938_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2938_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2938_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2938_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nExplanation: There is no mention of a film called \"The Time, the Place and the Girl\" in any of the documents. However, I can see that the text does talk about various films and film processes related to Vitaphone, such as \"Don Juan\", \"The Jazz Singer\", and Vitaphone shorts. But there is no specific mention of a film called \"The Time, the Place and the Girl\" being produced by Vitaphone."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the provided documents mention the film 'The Time, the Place and the Girl' or any connection between it and Vitaphone. The information in the documents is about the history and usage of the Vitaphone sound film system by Warner Bros., but there is no reference to a specific film being produced by Vitaphone."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context consistently describes Vitaphone as a sound film system used for productions by Warner Bros. and its sister studio First National from 1926 to 1931.  There's no mention of Vitaphone producing films outside this timeframe or with studios other than Warner Bros. and First National.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention the film \"The Time, the Place and the Girl\" at all.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention any film named 'The Time, the Place and the Girl' being produced by Vitaphone. The provided details focus on Vitaphone's usage by Warner Bros. and First National Pictures for feature films and short subjects from 1926 to 1930/1931, but do not include specific titles like 'The Time, the Place and the Girl'.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}